Core Technologies

- JavaScript
- React
- CSS/SCSS
- Tailwind CSS
- NextJS
- Node.js
- Prisma
- Google Firestore
- Framer Motion

Other skills

- Responsive Web Design
- UX/UI Design
- Git / GutHub
- Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator
- Figma
- Video editing (Final Cut Pro X)
- Digital Marketing
- Google Analytics
- Social Media Management

Content Creation & Storytelling

Wojciech Więcławski

Web Developer with corporate experiance

I'm a developer with 10 years of experience in the corporate world of Digital Marketing, Social Media, and Video Production. I am a Computer Science Engineer and have a Masters's degree in Management in Virtual Environments. My education and work experiance give me a deep understanding of the technical and business sides of digital projects.

Education

Poznań University of Technology

Computer Science (Engineer)

Poznan, Poland

Kozminski University

Management in Virtual Environments (e-business)

(Master's Degree)

Experience

Warsaw, Poland

Freelance - Web Developer, Social Media Strategist

Aug 2022 - Present

- Building web pages and web applications using React and Webflow • Developing social media strategy, creative content ideas, and conducting
- workshops and trainings.

Red Bull - Social Media Manager

Jan 2019 - Apr 2022

2012 - 2016

2016 - 2018

Warsaw, Poland

- Managing a team responsible for over 20 social media profiles (Facebook, Instagram, YouTube, TikTok, Discord)
- Content creation and curation across all channels and ensuring a cohesive online brand identity.
- Tracking and analyzing data to ensure a high engagement rate and driving users to owned channels.
- Planning and executing paid advertising. Preparing media plans, campaign optimization, and ongoing control of expenses. Depending on the campaign: from working with a media agency to working independently in Facebook's advertising system.
- Defining and developing social content creators and opinion leaders programs. Identifying and hiring new creators. Building long-term relationships.
- Digital projects management. Building and developing websites, platforms and digital experiences on redbull.com

Interesting projects

 Red Bull Enduro Liga - A platform that let us move Enduro-Motocross competitions to virtual world during the pandemic. Riders were uploading their video submitions throughtout 6 weeks period. Each entry was checked and judged by the admins. Platform was connected to Discord server.

Red Bull - Digital Specialist

Jun 2016 - Jan 2019

Warsaw, Poland

- Concept development and supervision of website creation for Red Bull projects.
- Developing, creating and implementing a communication plan in owned and managed media channels.
- Creating video content for social media and www. Depending on the project: cooperation with production teams or independent recording and editing.
- Support and implementation of tools extending the capabilities of redbull.com

Interesting projects

- Red Bull Wjazd na Bramkę Online platform for esport tournament in Rocket League. Team pairing, bracket generation, results submition and live result view during final stage of the project.
- Digital Activation for Red Bull Tour Bus music project. Users were asked to translate song lyrics to emojis and submit their creative work to the contest. App was generating graphics that were easily shareble in social medias.

Red Bull - Digital Marketing Trainee

Sep 2015 - Jun 2016

Warsaw, Poland

- Concept development and supervision of website creation for Red Bull projects.
- Developing, creating and implementing a communication plan in owned and managed media channels.
- Creating video content for social media and www. Depending on the project: cooperation with production teams or independent recording and editing.
- Support and implementation of tools extending the capabilities of redbull.com

Red Bull - Student Brand Manager

Apr 2012 - Jun 2015

- Poznan, Poland
- Brand ambasador working at Poznań University of Technology.
- Cooperation with student organizations in the city and supporting their initiatives.
- Organizing events for students.
- Maintaining good relations with local medias (radio stations, tvs, newspapers).

2010 - Sep 2015

Kitesurfing, Windsurfing and Skiing Instructor -

Poland, Greece, Brazil, Austria, France, Italy and more... • Group and individual lessons, mainly for adults. Teaching in Polish and English.